[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":2581,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":11660,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure that  when we  combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":12547,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":24210,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"34","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["34"],"rt":43372,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":67587,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":15243,"trial_type":"feedbac k","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":82835,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"9 ","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3","9 "],"rt":20695,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":103533,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":42739,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":146276,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start wi th the f irst number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":4901,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":151179,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":13317,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":164498,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1","2"],"rt":18031,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":182531,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":10606,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":193139,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":20157,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":213299,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":3436,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":216738,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":6910,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":223650,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1990,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":225644,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":9877,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":235523,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1248,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":236772,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's y our resu lt. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":6234,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":243009,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1496,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":244509,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":7468,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":251980,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1424,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":253406,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4531,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":257939,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1439,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":259379,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":10991,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":270375,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0 because 3 + 3 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1438,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":271814,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start  with th e first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":6838,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":278656,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 3 because 1 + 2 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1936,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":280595,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":8463,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":289061,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 4 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 6 = 4.","rt":1181,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":290244,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4981,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":295228,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0 because 4 + 2 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1247,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":296477,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4247,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":300725,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 2 because 0 + 2 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1542,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":302269,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0. 4-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3730,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":306000,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2 because 3 + 5 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1409,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":307412,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is  6 or bi gger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":8327,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":315742,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 because 1 + 4 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1110,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":316854,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4069,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":320926,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0 because 5 + 1 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1246,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":322173,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":7768,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":329942,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 1 because 1 + 0 = 1 and 1 is less than 6.","rt":1380,"trial_type":"fe edback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":331326,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4022,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":335350,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 1 because 5 + 2 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1097,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":336448,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.4-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we'v e learne d. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":9135,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":345588,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":1619,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":347208,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2","4"],"rt":11624,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":358836,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3428,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":362266,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4199,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":366475,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2062,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":368539,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4455,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":372997,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7- 0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2188,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":375188,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3248,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":378438,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1088,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":379532,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 .7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4296,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":383831,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1434,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":385268,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":40190,"trial_type":"instruct ions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":425460,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":12845,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":438308,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":5285,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":443596,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":5342,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":448940,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":4715,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":453656,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":2411,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":456070,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":3810,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":459884,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1543,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":461429,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":4981,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":466413,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1631,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":468045,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":16101,"trial_type":"instruct ions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":484148,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4773,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":488925,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1383,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":490309,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":8558,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":498869,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"W hat is 7  +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4376,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":503247,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4308,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":507558,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3452,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":511013,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"W hat is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4758,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":515772,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":4433,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":520207,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"I think if it is under 9 you don't have to subtract","explanation_history":["I think it","I think if it is under 9 you don't have to subtract"],"response_history":["I ","I","5"],"rt":28261,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":548469,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"I added 8 and 4 then subtracted 9","explanation_history":["I added 8 and 4 then subtracted 9"],"response_history":["4","3"],"rt":24166,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":572637,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"It is 9. ","explain":true,"explanation":"We subtract if the sum of the numbers is over 9","explanation_history":["We subtract if the sum of the numbers is over 9"],"response_history":["it ","it","i","It is 9.  If it is under 8 we keep the number but it","It is 9.  If it is under 8 we keep the number but if it is over 9 we subj","It is 9.  If it is under 8 we keep the nu","It is 9.  I","It is 9.  ","It is 9. "],"rt":39358,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":611997,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4997,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":616997,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2","92","9","2"],"rt":7351,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":624349,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":7623,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":631973,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"You don't have to subtract since the total is under 9","explanation_history":["Yo ","You don't have to subr","You don't have to subtrat","You don't have to subtract since the t otal is  under 3","You don't have to subtract since the total is under 9"],"response_history":["3"],"rt":33287,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":665262,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"I'm not sure but I think it is one of the numbers that isn't a generator","explanation_history":["I'm not sure but I think it is one of the numbers that isn't a generator"],"response_history":["No","Yes","No"],"rt":26790,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":692054,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"I don't think this is a generator under 9","explanation_history":["I don't think this is t","I don't think this is a gi","I don't think this is a generator o","I don't think this is a generator under 9"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":18724,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":710782,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Yes it is a generator but I'm not sure why","explanation_history":["Ye","Y","Yes it is a generator but I'm not sure why"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":14784,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":725567,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"I believe it is but I can't remember why","explanation_history":["Yes ","Yes","Ye","Y","I believe it is but I can't remember why"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":23077,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":748647,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":10678,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":759327,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 -n","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 -n"],"rt":10093,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":769422,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x+n","explain":true,"explanation":"I'm not sure I understand this one as well.","explanation_history":["I'm not sure I understand this one as well."],"response_history":["x+n"],"rt":16856,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":786279,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":" free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"by counting the numbers","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["by counting the numbers"],"rt":16102,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":802382,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":4294,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":89,"time_elapsed":806678,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":6184,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":90,"time_elapsed":812864,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":5365,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":91,"time_elapsed":818233,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"True","explain":true,"explanation":"Because it needs to be an even number","explanation_history":["Because  it need s to be an even number"],"response_history":["True"],"rt":17371,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":92,"time_elapsed":835607,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":6253,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":93,"time_elapsed":841862,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Always","explain":true,"explanation":"I believe it is but I can't put it into words","explanation_history":["I believe it is but I don't rmeem","I believe it is but I don't rmee","I believe it is but I don't rme","I believe it is but I don't rm","I believe it is but I don't remeber ","I believe it is but I don't ","I believe it is but I don't","I believe it is but I don'","I believe it is but I don","I believe it is but I do","I believe it is but I d","I believe it is but I ","I believe it is but I can't put it into words"],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":24470,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":94,"time_elapsed":866335,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Always","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":7222,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":95,"time_elapsed":873559,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2057,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":96,"time_elapsed":875617,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"44","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["44"],"rt":3262,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":97,"time_elapsed":878882,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Master s Degree ","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Associates Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Associates Degree"],"rt":3955,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":98,"time_elapsed":882839,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I have taken Statistics.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I h","I have stat","I have sta","I have st","I have s","I have taken Statistics."],"rt":12975,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":99,"time_elapsed":895817,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1  - never  heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":5117,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":100,"time_elapsed":900935,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"5 - used it, remember and understand it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"rt":7364,"trial_type":"questi on","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":101,"time_elapsed":908303,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":4653,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":102,"time_elapsed":912959,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":5278,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":103,"time_elapsed":918240,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enj oy this  HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":3027,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":104,"time_elapsed":921271,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Female"],"rt":2712,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":105,"time_elapsed":923985,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":5466,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":106,"time_elapsed":929455,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No I calculated in my head","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No I u","No I ","No I calculated in my head"],"rt":9246,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":107,"time_elapsed":938703,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I found it interesting that I could get the answers right but I have trouble putting it into words.  I could do most of them but I couldn't explain it.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I found it interesting that I could  get the  answers right but I have r","I found it interesting that I could get the answers right but I have troube pu","I found it interesting that I could get the answers right but I have troube p","I found it interesting that I could get the answers right but I have troube ","I found it interesting that I could get the answers right but I have troube","I found it interesting that I could get the answers right but I have trouble putting why ","I found it interesting that I could get the answers right but I have trouble putting why","I found it interesting that I could get the answers right but I have trouble putting wh","I found it interesting that I could get the answers right but I have trouble putting w","I found it interesting that I could get the answers right but I have trouble putting it into words.  I could do most of them but I couldn't explain it."],"rt":32214,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":108,"time_elapsed":970919,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15- 0"}]